Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
As friends, you already know me.
Brother, friends, I
already work here in ICICI Bank.
Friends, the topic of today's video here is that
if you want to get a job in ICICI Bank.
Friends, you
want to get a job directly in ICICI Bank, that too as a
Relationship Manager and
on a good salary package, so friends,
what did you have to do, ICIC had found a
solution for you here, whose
name was friends, the course which they had taken here, the
name of the course which they had taken was PO
Program, friends, there was a
course here, after doing which, friends,
you were directly
given the post of Relationship Manager in ICICI Bank.  Friends, what I am going to
tell you in today's video is
that right now the PO program of ICICI here has been
100% closed.
Right now you might be seeing it here on the website.
But friends, it is 100% closed here.
Those who are currently in the PO
program, either they have an
interview here or they have an assessment
test or they have received the link.  The
interview date has arrived.  The
link regarding the interview has already been sent here
or the city is not getting selected here.
So friends, the
reason for this is going to be that the
PO program of ICICI has been
closed here.  Friends, why has ICICI
closed this here
?  In today's video,
you are going to know about it in full detail.
Friends, will ICICI's PO
program be reopened again
or friends, there could be some
big reason for this, otherwise friends, if
you want to do a job in ICICI Bank, then
brother, do you have any option left here,
friends, there is
a reason for the course which has been closed here, I am going to
tell you that in today's video.  Complete
information regarding this course is
available here in today's video.  For this,
friends, you have to do only one thing.   If you like the
video, please give it a like.  If you are
new to the channel then friends, you have to
subscribe to the channel because
friends, you keep getting such content here.
Without wasting any time let's
start the video.  Friends, I have
directly opened its website here.
Well, brother, if you
check now, you will go to the website of ICICI here
and brother, if you check, then brother, at this
time, friends, the program will be
shown here right now.  I mean,
I just checked here.  I am
checking it in front of you.  So brother, a
show is going on here near me also.  But brother,
what is the problem here, as far as
I know, the
course here has been
closed here.
Why has it been closed?  Friends,
you already
know the big reason behind this.  If brother, you do not
know then brother, you will find a link
of the banker program below.  So
friends, you can go and watch it here.
They have
launched a course here which is named
Aspire Bank program.  Friends, the
course is going to be free of cost here.
You have 2 months of training.  The
grade that you
get here, brother,
you get a good grade here.  In this, your
salary here ranges from ₹45 lakh
to ₹5.5 lakh.
Well,
friends, this program is here.   It is
eligible for both freshers and experienced people here.  Friends, if you want to apply here then
you can apply for Aspire Bank program.
You will find the link
of that video here in the description box.
You can go and watch that video here.  You will get to
know the complete details here.  Rest
friends, today's update here is
that the PO program of ICICI here has been
100% closed here.  Those whose interview is
not getting scheduled, whose city
etc. is not getting selected here, then
brother, the reason for this is that your
course here, which is your PO program, has been
closed.
Friends, the MoneyPayal site has been closed here.
Now brother, if you look at it,
you will not see any ads etc. here.  Like
you used to get ads etc. on Facebook.
Those friends, ads etc. have also been closed here.
Friends, in a few days,
in 4 to 5 days, he is going to
remove it from his website also.
And brother, here the PO program of ICICI has been
100% closed.  Rest of the
friends, you can check it out here by
visiting their website.  Friends, I have
already done it, its PO program has been
closed here.
And friends,
why have they closed it here?  The reason is
that brother, their Aspire Bank
program here is also trending here.
Many children from there are
coming here and brother, they are also getting selected here.  The
training that is taking place here
, brother, there is
a university here in Neemrana, NIT here.
Friends, after going there, their
training is going on here.  Friends of some people, I have already got them
selected here.
I have already received offer letters from some of them.  And
brother, if you join the Aspire Bank program.
In that, friends,
you have to give a test at your place.  In that, friends,
you have to give an interview face to face.
Brothers, whatever preparation is there for the interview, we
take 100 to 100% guarantee here that we provide training for it here.  Friends,
if you do it here at a very affordable price, then you will have a
face to face introduction here.  100 to 100%
friends, your face to face intro here will be
100%
clear to you here.  If brother,
you join our training here.
Friends, we have arranged training for
Aspire Bank's program here at an affordable price.
Friends, what do you have to do for this?  Below is the link
of the WhatsApp group,
friends, you will get
my number there.  After that you have to send me a message
and brother, you have to write
training there.  So brother, the details will be shared with you.
Today's
main topic of the video is going to be about the
PO program, which has been
closed here at present.
Friends, what is going on here at present is the program of Aspire Bank.
Brother,
some criteria have been kept for you in this.  Like
you will need 60% in your 10th.
You will need 60% in 12th also and brother,
you will
need 60% in your graduation also.  Only after that
friends, you can apply in it.  There will be 100%
sales jobs here.
You are about to get the grade of Deputy Manager.
D One You will get your grade here.
Rest of the brothers, you will get to see packages here from ₹45 lakh to ₹5.55 lakh.
Friends, the course here is very
good.  If you want to do it brother,
you can do it here.  Rest of the friends,
in today's video I have told you that the
PO program of ICICI has been
closed.  I hope you liked this information
in today's video.  If you liked the
video, please give it a like.
Friends, if you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then
brother,
please go quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.  Till then
take care.